Harold H. Burton Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Supreme Court File, 1792-1965 (Box 56-325)
  - Correspondence, 1936-1965 (Box 56-125)
    - October term 1956
      - United States v. E. I. du Pont de Nemours and Co., 1957
      - University of Chicago, Chicago, Ill., 1956-1957
      - “U” miscellaneous, 1957
      - Vacation, 1956-1957, (2 folders)
      - “V” miscellaneous, 1957
      - Warren, Earl, 1957
      - “W-Z” miscellaneous, 1957, (3 folders)
    - October term 1957 (Box 112)
      - American Bar Association, 1958
      - American Legion, 1958
      - Arnold, Stanley N., 1958
      - Autograph requests, 1958, (2 folders)
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1957-1958, (2 folders)
      - Birthday greetings, 1958
      - Bowdoin Prize, Bowdoin College, Brunswick, Maine, 1958-1959, (2 folders)
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1958, (2 folders)
      - Condolences, 1958, undated
      - Crank letters, 1958
      - Cuyahoga County, Ohio, board of elections, 1958
      - “C” miscellaneous, 1958, undated, (3 folders)
      - Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1958
      - “D” miscellaneous, 1957-1958
      - “E” miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 113)
      - Forkosch, Morris D., 1958
      - “F-G” miscellaneous, 1958, (2 folders)
      - Hotel Cleveland, Cleveland, Ohio, 1957-1958
      - “H” miscellaneous, 1958
      - Invitations accepted, 1957-1958
      - Invitations declined, 1958
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1958
      - Judicial Conference of the Sixth Circuit, Ann Arbor, Mich., 1957-1958
      - “J-K” miscellaneous, 1958, (2 folders)
      - Law and Order (magazine), 1958
      - Law clerk applications, 1957-1958, (2 folders)
      - Law clerks appointed, 1957-1958
      - Luncheon for members of the Court, 1957-1958
      - “L-M” miscellaneous, 1958, (4 folders)
      - New York University School of Law, New York, N.Y., 1958
      - “N” miscellaneous, 1958
      - Opinions by the Court, reaction to, 1958, undated (Box 114)
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1958
      - Publications received, 1957-1958
      - Person to Person (television interview program), 1958-1959, (2 folders)
      - “P-Q” miscellaneous, 1957-1958
      - Retirement
        - Letter of resignation to Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1958
        - Miscellany, 1958
          - A-Mc, (10 folders)
          - Me-Z, (5 folders) (Box 115)
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1958
      - Segregation cases, 1956-1957, undated
      - Sessions, Gilpin S., 1958
      - Students, meetings with, 1958, (2 folders)
      - Switzerland, family and friends, 1956-1958
      - “S-T” miscellaneous, 1957-1958, (3 folders)
      - University of Cincinnati College of Law, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1958
      - “U” miscellaneous, 1958
      - Vacation, 1958
      - “V” miscellaneous, 1958
      - Warren, Earl, 1958 (Box 116)
      - “W” miscellaneous, 1957-1958
      - Yee-Quil, Cornelia N., 1957-1958
      - “Y-Z” miscellaneous, 1958
    - Retired status
      - Administrative Office of the United States Courts, Washington, D.C., 1959-1964, undated
      - America Illustrated, 1959-1962
      - American Association for Hospital Planning, award, 1961
      - American Bar Association, 1959-1963
      - American Journal of Legal History, 1959-1962
      - American Legion, 1959-1963
      - American Society for Friendship with Switzerland, 1959-1963, (2 folders)
      - American Society for Legal History
        - Essay contest, 1959-1960
        - Miscellany, 1958-1962, (2 folders)
      - Amstel, T. J. van, 1959-1960
      - Arnold, Stanley, 1960-1964, (2 folders)
      - Autograph requests, 1959-1964, (4 folders)
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1959-1964, undated, (3 folders) (Box 117)
      - Baily, Howard J., 1959-1964
      - Bar Association of the District of Columbia, 1959-1963
      - Birthday greetings, 1959-1964, (5 folders)
      - Bowdoin College, Brunswick, Maine
        - Class of 1909, 1960, (2 folders)
        - Fiftieth reunion
          - Brewster, Owen, 1959, undated, (3 folders)
          - Miscellany, 1959, (2 folders)
          - Rich, Irving, 1959 (Box 118)
        - Miscellany, 1961-1964, undated, (3 folders)
        - Review of Spruce Head by Wilbert Snow, 1959-1960
      - Brewster, Owen, 1959-1963
      - Burton, Selma F. S., 1964
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1958-1964, (4 folders)
      - Case, William Lyman, 1962
      - Clark, Charles P., 1959-1963
      - Clark, Tom C., 1959-1961
      - Cleveland, Ohio, board of elections, 1959-1964
      - Cleveland Bar Association, Cleveland, Ohio, award, 1962
      - Cleveland Chamber of Commerce, Cleveland, Ohio, award, 1962
      - Cleveland Men's Club of Washington, D.C., award, 1964-1965, (4 folders)
      - Cleveland Plain Dealer, 1959-1962
      - Cleveland Press, 1960-1962
      - Clothey, Thomas L., 1959-1963 (Box 119)
      - Condolences, 1960-1963
      - Crampton, Roger C., 1959-1962
      - Crank letters, 1945-1964, (2 folders)
      - “C” miscellaneous, 1959-1964, (3 folders)
      - Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1959-1962, undated
      - Desk and Derrick Club of Washington, D.C., 1959
      - “D-E” miscellaneous, 1955-1964, (4 folders)
      - Finances, 1963-1964
      - Freemasons, 1959-1961
      - “F” miscellaneous, 1959-1964, (2 folders)
      - George Washington University, Washington, D.C., 1958-1963
      - “G” miscellaneous, 1959-1963
      - Hallmark Cards, Inc., 1961
      - Harold Hitz Burton Beneficiary Aid Fund, Harvard Law School, 1964
      - Hart, Earl E., 1959-1965, (2 folders) (Box 120)
      - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass., 1961-1963
      - Hiram College, Hiram, Ohio, 1961-1964, (2 folders)
      - Hitz, Frederick P., 1959-1961
      - Hotel Cleveland, Cleveland, Ohio, 1959-1963
      - “H” miscellaneous, 1958-1964, (3 folders)
      - Invitations accepted, 1958-1964, (3 folders)
      - Invitations declined
        - 1959-1962
        - 1963-1964 (Box 121)
      - “I-J” miscellaneous, 1959-1964, (2 folders)
      - Kennedy, John F., inaugural ceremonies, 1960-1961
      - Kiwanis Club of Cleveland, Ohio, 1958-1963
      - “K” miscellaneous, 1959-1964, (2 folders)
      - Lafferty, A. W., 1957-1960
      - Law clerks
        - Applications, 1962-1964
        - Dinner, 1960
        - Miscellany, 1956-1964
      - Lentz, John and Alice, 1959-1964
      - Lingelbach, Louis, 1960-1964
      - Luncheon for members of the Court, 1959-1964, (6 folders)
      - “L” miscellaneous, 1958-1964, (2 folders)
      - Macauley, Frederick P., 1956-1959
      - Memberhips, 1963-1964
      - Mitchell, Isabella E., 1959-1964 (Box 122)
      - “M” miscellaneous, 1958-1964, (6 folders)
      - New York University School of Law, New York, N.Y., 1958-1963
      - “N” miscellaneous, 1959-1963, (2 folders)
      - Ogawa, Tatsu, 1959-1964
      - Ohio State University College of Law, Columbus, Ohio, building dedication, 1959-1960
      - Opinions by the Court, reaction to, 1959-1963, (3 folders)
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1959-1963, (2 folders)
      - Parkinson's disease
        - 1959
        - 1960-1964 (Box 123)
      - Phi Alpha Delta Law Fraternity, 1959-1963
      - Press Club of Ohio, Columbus, Ohio, 1959
      - “P” miscellaneous, 1959-1964, (2 folders)
      - Rood, Arnold C., 1962
      - Rotary Club of Cleveland, Ohio, 1959-1963
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1958-1963, (2 folders)
      - Salvation Army, 1959-1964
      - Segregation, 1957-1959, undated, (3 folders)
      - Sessions, Gilpin S., 1959-1964
      - Students, meetings with, 1959
      - Switzerland, family and friends, 1959-1963, (2 folders)
      - “Sa” miscellaneous, 1960-1964
      - “Sc-Sw” miscellaneous, 1959-1963, (4 folders) (Box 124)
      - Travel itineraries, 1964, undated
      - “T” miscellaneous, 1958-1964, (3 folders)
      - Uhrig, Ann, 1960-1964
      - Unitarian churches, 1958-1964, (2 folders)
      - “U” miscellaneous, 1959-1963
      - Vacations, 1959-1962, (3 folders)
      - Volta Bureau, Washington, D.C., 1959-1964
      - “V” miscellaneous, 1959-1962
      - Warren, Earl, 1959-1964, (2 folders)
      - Wellesley College, Wellesley, Mass., 1962-1963
      - Wiley, Harvey W., 1960
      - “W” miscellaneous, 1959-1964, (3 folders)
      - Yee-Quil, Cornelia N., 1959-1964 (Box 125)
      - YMCA
        - Award, 1959
        - Miscellany, 1959-1964, (2 folders)
      - “Y” miscellaneous, 1959
  - Case File, 1944-1960 (Box 125-308)
    Printed, typed and handwritten copies of opinions, copies of circulated opinions, memoranda by justices and law clerks (including bench and certiorari memoranda), briefs, notes, transcripts, reports, docket sheets, and conference lists.
    Grouped chronologically by the Court's annual October terms. Arranged alphabetically within each term by type of material or docket and chronologically or numerically by docket number therein. Material for individual opinions is filed alphabetically by type of material.
    - October term 1944 (Box 125)
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - North Am. Co. v. Securites & Exchange Comm'n, 1
    - October term 1945
      - Conference lists, 1945-1946, (3 folders)
      - Dockets, (1 vol.) (Box 126)
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Appellate docket
          - 1-56, (4 folders)
          - 58-428, (13 folders) (Box 127)
          - 429-970, (13 folders) (Box 128)
          - 971-1304, (4 folders) (Box 129)
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Miscellaneous docket, 1-130, (2 folders)
        - Original docket, 9
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - Securities & Exchange Comm'n v. Engineers Pub. Serv. Co., 2; (2 folders)
          - Engineers Pub. Serv. Co. v. Securities & Exchange Comm'n See same container, 2, 3
          - New York v. United States, 5
          - United Bhd. of Carpenters v. United States, 9
          - Bay Counties Dist. Council, United Bhd. of Carpenters v. United States See same container, 9, 10
          - Lumber Prods. Ass'n v. United States See same container, 9, 11
          - Alameda County Bldg. & Constr. Trades Council v. United States See same container, 9, 12
          - Boorman Lumber Co. v. United States See same container, 9, 13
          - Duncan v. Kahanamoku, 14; (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 130)
          - White v. Steer See Container 129, 14, 15
          - Hawk v. Olson, 17
          - American Tobacco Co. v. United States, 18; (5 folders)
          - Liggett & Myers Tobacco Co. v. United States See same container, 18, 19
          - R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Co. v. United States See same container, 18, 20
          - Martino v. Michigan Window Cleaning Co., 21; (4 folders)
          - United States v. Detroit and Cleveland Navigation Co., 22
          - Order of Ry. Conductors v. Pitney, 37
          - May Dep't Store Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., 39 (Box 131)
          - Bollenbach v. United States, 41
          - Thompson v. Texas Mexican Ry., 42
          - Keeton v. Thompson, 43
          - United States v. American Union Transp., 44
          - Roland Elec. Co. v. Walling, 45; (8 folders)
          - General Elec. Co. v. Jewel Incandescent Lamp Co., 46 (Box 132)
          - Bailey v. Anderson, 49
          - Better Business Bureau v. United States, 52
          - Gange Lumber Co. v. Rowley, 53
          - Scott Paper Co. v. Marcalus Mfg. Co., 54
          - United States v. New York Tel. Co., 55
          - Kirby Petroleum Co. v. Commissioner, 56
          - Mabee v. White Plains Publishing Co., 57
          - Oklahoma Press Publishing Co. v. Walling, 61
          - News Printing Co. v. Walling See same container, 61, 63
          - Ashbacker Radio Corp. v. Federal Communications Comm'n, 65
          - Smith v. United States See Container 133, 292, 66
          - Boehm v. Commissioner, 69
          - Mine Safety Appliances Co. v. Forrestal, 71
          - Nippert v. City of Richmond, 72
          - Boutell v. Walling, 73; (4 folders)
          - United States v. Pierce Auto Freight Lines, 74
          - Markham v. Cabell, 76; (4 folders)
          - United States v. Petty Motor Co., 77
          - United States v. Brockbank See same container, 77, 78
          - United States v. Grimsdell See same container, 77, 79
          - United States v. Wiggs See same container, 77, 80
          - United States v. Independent Pneumatic Tool Co. See same container, 77, 81
          - United States v. Galigher Co. See same container, 77, 82
          - United States v. Gray-Cannon Lumber Co. See same container, 77, 83
          - Griffin v. Griffin, 86
          - Tucker v. Texas, 87
          - Hercules Gasoline Co. v. Commissioner, 93
          - International Shoe Co. v. State of Washington, 107
          - Marsh v. Alabama See same container, 87, 114
          - United States v. Johnson, 115
          - United States v. Sommers See Container 132, 115, 116 (Box 133)
          - Fisher v. United States, 122
          - Williams v. United States, 123; (6 folders)
          - Canizio v. New York, 152
          - Elgin, Joliet & E. Ry. v. Burley, 160
          - Commissioner v. Wilcox, 163; (2 folders)
          - Chickasaw Nation v. United States, 170
          - Commissioner v. Crawford See Container 132, 56, 197
          - M. Kraus & Bros., Inc. v. United States, 198
          - Hulbert v. Twin Falls County, 238
          - S.R.A. Inc. v. Minnesota, 254
          - S.R.A. Inc. v. Minnesota See same container, 254, 255
          - Lusthaus v. Commissioner, 263
          - Robertson v. California, 274
          - Reconstruction Fin. Corp. v. Denver & Rio Grande W. R.R., 278
          - Reconstruction Fin. Corp. v. Denver & Salt Lake W. R.R. See same container, 278, 279
          - Reconstruction Fin. Corp. v. City Bank Farmers Trust See same container, 278, 280
          - Reconstruction Fin. Corp. v. Denver & Rio Grande W. R.R. See same container, 278, 281
          - Reconstruction Fin. Corp. v. Thompson See same container, 278, 282
          - Allen v. Trust Co. of Ga., 289
          - Estep v. United States, 292; (1 folder) (Box 134)
          - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Cheney, Calif., Lumber Co., 319
          - Wilson v. Cook, 328
          - Cook v. Wilson See same container, 328, 329
          - Anderson v. Mt. Clemens Pottery Co., 342
          - Bell v. Hood, 344
          - Thiel v. Southern Pac. Co., 349
          - Burton-Sutton Oil Co. v. Commissioner, 361
          - Seas Shipping Co. v. Sieracki, 365
          - Smith v. Hoboken R.R., 384
          - Meyer v. Fleming, 392
          - Hannegan v. Esquire, Inc., 399
          - Davis v. United States, 404
          - Swanson v. Marra Bros., Inc., 405
          - United States v. Rice, 411
          - Duggan v. Sansberry, 418
          - National Aircraft Corp. v. Sansberry See same container, 418, 419
          - Kennecott Copper Co. v. State Tax Comm'r, 424
          - Silver King Coalition Mines Co. v. State Tax Comm'r See same container, 424, 425
          - El Dorado Oil Works v. United States, 428
          - American Fed'n of Labor v. Watson, 448
          - Kotteakos v. United States, 457
          - Reganbogen v. United States See same container, 457, 458
          - Pennekamp v. Florida, 473
          - United States v. Carbone, 474
          - Poff v. Pennsylvania R.R. Co., 484
          - Heiser v. Woodruff, 496
          - Holmberg v. Armbrecht, 505
          - Knauer v. United States, 510
          - D. A. Schulte, Inc. v. Gangi, 517
          - Joseph v. Carter & Weekes Stevedoring Co., 518
          - Joseph v. Clark & Son See same container, 518, 519
          - United States v. Welch, 528
          - United States v. Burns See same container, 528, 529
          - United States v. Lollis See same container, 528, 530
          - United States v. Bradshaw See same container, 528, 531
          - United States v. Rust See same container, 528, 532
          - United States v. Hyatt See same container, 528, 533
          - Lavender v. Kurn, 550
          - Order of United Commercial Travelers v. Wolfe, 556
          - Girouard v. United States, 572
          - First Iowa Hydro-Elec. Coop. v. Federal Power Comm'n, 603; (3 folders); (7 folders) (Box 135)
          - Jacob Siegel Co. v. Federal Trade Comm'n, 605
          - McAllister Lighterage Line v. United States, 616
          - Hust v. Moore-McCormack Lines, 625
          - United States v. Causby, 630
          - Yamashita v. Styer See Container 136, 61 Misc., 672
          - Bihn v. United States, 675
          - United States v. Joseph A. Holpuch Co., 696
          - United States v. Joseph A. Holpuch Co. See same container, 696, 697
          - Morgan v. Virginia, 704; (4 folders)
          - Prudential Ins. Co. v. Benjamin, 707
          - Pinkerton v. United States, 719 (Box 136)
          - Illinois ex rel. Gordon v. United States, 749
          - Queenside Hills Realty Co. v. Saxl, 769
          - Porter v. Warner Holding Co., 793
          - United States v. Lovett, 809
          - United States v. Watson See same container, 809, 810
          - United States v. Dodd See same container, 809, 811
          - Securities & Exch. Comm'n v. W. J. Howey & Co., 843
          - Fishgold v. Sullivan Drydock & Repair Corp., 970
          - Porter v. Lee, 1116
          - Porter v. Lee See same container, 1116, 1117
          - Porter v. Dicken See same container, 1116, 1118
        - Miscellaneous docket
          - In re Yamashita, 61 Misc.; (5 folders)
          - In re Homma, 93 Misc.
    - October term 1946
      - Conference lists, 1946-1947, (4 folders)
      - Dockets
        - Appellate
          - Index
          - 1-49
          - 50-1450, (12 folders) (Box 137)
          - 1451-1512 (Box 138)
        - Miscellaneous, 1-154
        - Original, 6-12
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Appellate docket
          - Argued cases
            - 3-88, (12 folders)
            - 89-658, (15 folders) (Box 139)
            - 673-1389, (5 folders) (Box 140)
          - Certiorari denied and appeals dismissed
            - 99-380, (10 folders)
            - 381-834, (14 folders) (Box 141)
            - 835-1216, (13 folders) (Box 142)
            - 1217-1508, (8 folders) (Box 143)
        - Miscellaneous docket, 1-154, unnumbered, and various petitions for rehearings, (3 folders)
        - Original docket
          - Argued case, 10
          - Case disposed of or removed from the docket, 9
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - Levinson v. Spector Motor Serv., 22; (4 folders); (12 folders); (3 folders) (Box 144, Box 145)
          - Order of United Commercial Travelers of Am. v. Wolfe, 32; (11 folders); (3 folders) (Box 146)
          - Ballard v. United States, 37; (6 folders)
          - United States v. Carmack, 40; (6 folders) (Box 147)
          - United States v. Carmack, (3 folders) (Box 148)
          - Pyramid Motor Freight Corp. v. Ispass, 41; (9 folders)
          - United States v. National Lead Co., 89; (3 folders); (6 folders) (Box 149, Box 150)
          - National Lead Co. v. United States See Container 148, 89, 90
          - E. I. du Pont de Nemours & Co. v. United States See Container 148, 89, 91
          - Louisiana ex rel. Francis v. Resweber, 142; (6 folders); (3 folders) (Box 151)
          - Myers v. Reading Co., 367; (9 folders)
        - Miscellaneous docket
          - In re Durant, 19 Misc.
    - October term 1947
      - Conference lists
        - 1947, (2 folders)
        - 1948, undated, (6 folders) (Box 152)
      - Dockets
        - Appellate
          - Index
          - 1-850, unnumbered, (9 folders)
        - Miscellaneous, 1-571, unnumbered, (3 folders) (Box 153)
        - Original, unnumbered
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Appellate docket
          - Argued cases
            - 3-78, (10 folders)
            - 79-569, (13 folders) (Box 154)
            - 583-775, (2 folders) (Box 155)
          - Certiorari denied and appeals dismissed
            - 9-492, (12 folders)
            - 493-850, (14 folders) (Box 156)
        - Miscellaneous docket (Box 157)
          - 1-525, (14 folders)
          - 526-571, (2 folders) (Box 158)
        - Original docket, 9
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - Morris v. McComb, 7; (7 folders)
          - United States v. Line Material Co., 8; (5 folders); (10 folders); (2 folders) (Box 159, Box 160)
          - United States v. United States Gypsum Co., 13
          - Federal Trade Comm'n v. Cement Inst., 23; (3 folders); (6 folders) (Box 161)
          - Federal Trade Comm'n v. Aetna Portland Cement Co. See Container 160, 23, 24
          - Federal Trade Comm'n v. Marquette Cement Mfg. Co. See Container 160, 23, 25
          - Federal Trade Comm'n v. Calaveras Cement Co. See Container 160, 23, 26
          - Federal Trade Comm'n v. Huron Portland Cement Co. See Container 160, 23, 27
          - Federal Trade Comm'n v. Superior Portland Cement, Inc. See Container 160, 23, 28
          - Federal Trade Comm'n v. Northwestern Portland Cement Co. See Container 160, 23, 29
          - Federal Trade Comm'n v. Riverside Cement Co. See Container 160, 23, 30
          - Federal Trade Comm'n v. Universal Atlas Cement Co. See Container 160, 23, 31
          - Federal Trade Comm'n v. California Portland Cement Co. See Container 160, 23, 32
          - Federal Trade Comm'n v. Monolith Portland Cement Co. See Container 160, 23, 33
          - Federal Trade Comm'n v. Smith See Container 160, 23, 34
          - Maggio v. Zeitz, 38; (2 folders)
          - International Salt Co. v. United States, 46
          - Donaldson v. Read Magazine, 50; (3 folders)
          - Haley v. Ohio, 51; (7 folders) (Box 162)
          - Estate of Spiegal v. Commissioner See also Containers 163, 96, and 173, 3, 52; (2 folders)
          - Rodgers v. United States, 58; (2 folders)
          - Von Moltke v. Gillies, 73; (2 folders); (5 folders) (Box 163)
          - Pownall v. United States See same container, 105, 74
          - Illinois ex rel. McCollum v. Board of Educ., 90; (4 folders)
          - Alexander Wool Combing Co. v. United States See same container, 105, 95
          - Commissioner v. Estate of Church See also Containers 162, 52, and 173, 5, 96
          - Lichter v. United States, 105; (4 folders); (10 folders) (Box 164)
          - Funk Brothers Seed Co. v. Kalo Inoculant Co., 280
          - Bute v. Illinois, 398; (2 folders); (6 folders) (Box 165)
          - Taylor v. Alabama, 721; (10 folders)
    - October term 1948 (Box 166)
      - Conference lists, 1948-1949, (8 folders)
      - Dockets
        - Appellate
          - Index
          - 1-749, (6 folders)
          - 750-877, 1388, unnumbered (Box 167)
        - Miscellaneous, 1-692, (3 folders)
        - Original, 10
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Appellate docket
          - Argued cases
            - 1-51, (9 folders)
            - 52-406, (13 folders) (Box 168)
            - 416-671, (5 folders) (Box 169)
          - Certiorari denied and appeals dismissed
            - 43-264, (10 folders)
            - 268-594, (15 folders) (Box 170)
            - 595-877, (10 folders) (Box 171)
        - Miscellaneous
          - 2-134, (4 folders)
          - 135-687, (15 folders) (Box 172)
          - 688-692 (Box 173)
        - Original, 9
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - Estate of Spiegal v. Commissioner See also same container, 5, and Container 162, 52, 3; (11 folders)
          - Commissioner v. Estate of Church See also same container, 3, and Container 163, 96, 5; (1 folder); (10 folders) (Box 174)
          - Grand River Dam Auth. v. Grand-Hydro Corp., 6; (3 folders); (5 folders) (Box 175)
          - Brinegar v. United States, 12; (2 folders)
          - Commissioner v. Jacobson, 32; (6 folders); (2 folders) (Box 176)
          - Commissioner v. Jacobson See Container 175, 32, 33
          - Goggin v. Division of Labor Law Enforcement, 35; (7 folders)
          - McDonald v. United States, 36; (2 folders)